Keys mss., 1972-1982 LMC 2716
Lilly Library
- Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Individuals and Organizations (Box 1)
    - United Nations Office for Inter-, 1974 (Box 3)
    - United Nations Office of Public Information., 1973-1977 (Box 3)
    - United Nations Reform Electoral Campaign Committee., 1977 (Box 3)
    - United Nations Study Group., 1974 (Box 3)
    - United Nations We Believe., 1973 (Box 3)
    - United Peoples., 1973 (Box 3)
    - United States Arms Control and Disarmament Agency., 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - United States Senate., 1972-1976 (Box 3)
    - United World Federalists of Japan., 1976-1978 (Box 3)
    - United World Federalists of Japan Youth and Student Division., 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - Université Laval., 1974 (Box 3)
    - University of Canterbury Department of Political Science., 1974 (Box 3)
    - University of Michigan Ann Arbor., 1973 (Box 3)
    - University of Pennsylvania University Museum., 1974 (Box 3)
    - University of Wisconsin-, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
    - Unnerstall, Roy., 1975 (Box 3)
    - Urquhart, Brian., 1972-1973 (Box 3)
    - Bakay van Dapperen, Thea., 1975 (Box 3)
    - Vaughan, Paula., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Vickers, Burnell., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Victor, Mary., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Villanova University., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Wadlow, Rene., 1974-1978 (Box 3)
    - Waeber, Zelda M., 1974 (Box 3)
    - Wagner, Christopher A., 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - Wayne State University Center for Teaching about Peace and War., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Watson, Irene., 1974 (Box 3)
    - War/Peace Report., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Waterlow, Charlotte., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Webb, Aileen., 1977 (Box 3)
    - Webster, Lucy., 1968-1981 (Box 3)
    - Wellesley-Welsey, James., 1972 (Box 3)
    - Wereld Federalisten Beweging Nederland., 1972-1975 (Box 3)
    - Wesselman, Nancy., 1972-1973 (Box 3)
    - Weston, Burns H., 1972-1973 (Box 3)
    - Whitaker, Urban., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Wickersham, William., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Wiener, Annabella., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Wiley, Karla., 1972 (Box 3)
    - Williams, Stillman P., 1972 (Box 3)
    - Wilmington College., 1974 (Box 3)
    - Wilson, Edward B., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Wilson, H. Donald., 1974-1976 (Box 3)
    - Wingate, Monica M., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Wiseberg, Laura., 1978 (Box 3)
    - Wiseman, Harry., 1974 (Box 3)
    - World Magazine., 1972-1973 (Box 3)
    - World Association of World Federalists., 1972-1982 (Box 3)
    - World Association of World Federalists Task Force "SUN.", 1972-1978 (Box 3)
    - World Association of World Federalists World Federalist Youth., 1974-1976 (Box 3)
    - World Citizens Assembly., 1974 (Box 3)
    - World Conference of Religion for Peace., 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - World Constitution and Parliament Association., 1972-1973 (Box 3)
    - World Federal Authority Committee., 1975-1976 (Box 3)
    - World Federalist Educational Fund., 1972-1975 (Box 3)
    - World Federalist Magazine., 1972-1974 (Box 3)
    - World Federalist Political Education Committee., 1977 (Box 3)
    - World Federalist Youth., 1974 (Box 3)
    - World Federalist Youth, USA., 1973 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists Association., 1973-1982 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists Association Capital Distract Chapter., 1978 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists Association Esperanto Section., 1976 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists Association New England., 1977-1978 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists Association of Pittsburgh., 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists Associations Switzerland., 1976 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists of Canada., 1972-1982 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists of Canada Hamilton Branch., 1976-1977 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists Philadelphia Area Council., 1973 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists, USA., 1972-1974 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists, USA Baltimore Area Council., 1972-1974 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists, USA Cape and Islands Chapter., 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists, USA Consultation on Constituencies for Change., 1972 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists, USA New Jersey Branch., 1972-1974 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists, USA Northeast Region., 1973 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists, USA Oregon Branch., 1974 (Box 3)
    - World Federalists, USA Southern California Branch., 1973 (Box 3)
    - World Federation Research Institute., 1976 (Box 3)
    - World Goodwill., 1973 (Box 3)
    - World Journal of Psychosynthesis., 1972 (Box 3)
    - World Order Studies Project., 1977 (Box 3)
    - World Peace Movement for World Federal Government., 1973 (Box 3)
    - World Population Society., 1976 (Box 3)
    - World Union., 1974 (Box 3)
    - World View., 1972-1973 (Box 3)
    - Worthington, Oliver J., 1976 (Box 3)
    - Wyndham, R. H., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Wyvell, Mary L., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Yost, Charles W., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Young, Andrew., 1977 (Box 3)
    - Young, Clarence., 1976 (Box 3)
    - Young, Kenneth., 1974 (Box 3)
    - Young, Virginia B., 1975 (Box 3)
    - Younghouse, Paul., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Zijlstra, Bauwke., 1977 (Box 3)
    - Zimba, G. R., 1974 (Box 3)
    - Zion, Leonard., 1973 (Box 3)
    - Zwingeberg, Linda A., 1975 (Box 3)
  - Diplomatic Correspondence (Box 4)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 4)
    - 1971 (Box 4)
    - 1972 (Box 4)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 4)
- World Association of World Federalists' (WAWF) Projects (Box 4)
  Arranged alphabetically within each subseries: Reports and Accompanying Records; Meetings and Conferences; and Speaking Engagements.
  - Reports and Accompanying Records (Box 4)
    - Appeal to the World's People., 1970 (Box 4)
    - ATOM Committee., 1974 (Box 4)
    - Book Originals., 1972 (Box 4)
    - Disarmament, National Security and the U.S. Citizen., 1979 (Box 4)
    - East Pakistan Resolution., 1971 (Box 4)
    - Finances., 1973-1976 (Box 4)
    - Human Manifesto., 1966-1970 (Box 4)
    - INTELSAT., 1970 (Box 4)
    - International Reports., 1979-1980 (Box 4)
    - Interview Notes., 1969-1971 (Box 4)
    - Kettering Foundation., 1970-1975 (Box 4)
    - Middle East Peacekeeping Simulation Project., 1972-1973 (Box 4)
    - Non-Governmental Organization Applications ECOSOC., 1969-1977 (Box 4)
    - Non-Governmental Organization Liaison Policy., 1969-1975 (Box 4)
    - Pledge of United Nations Citizenship., 1970 (Box 4)
    - Press Clippings., 1969-1973 (Box 4)
    - Principles of a Peaceful Settlement in the Middle East., 1973-1974 (Box 4)
    - Reports of the UN General Assembly., 1973-1975 (Box 4)
    - Sample Mailings., 1972-1973 (Box 4)
    - Statement of the NGO Representatives on the Situation in Cyprus., 1974-1975 (Box 4)
    - Statutes and Policies., 1968-1974 (Box 4)
    - Strategy., 1969-1971 (Box 4)
    - To Strengthen the United Nations., 1969-1970 (Box 4)
    - U Thant Farewell Tribute., 1971 (Box 4)
    - United Nations Charter Review Resolutions., 1970-1972 (Box 4)
    - US ACDA., 1971 (Box 4)
    - Visitation Campaign., 1970-1973 (Box 4)
    - WAWF Council., 1976-1979 (Box 4)
    - WAWF Disarmament Resolution., 1973 (Box 4)
    - WAWF Reception., 1978 (Box 4)
    - World Conference of Religion for Peace., 1972 (Box 4)
    - World Federalists USA., 1976-1979 (Box 5)
    - WFUSA/WAWF Memos., 1977-1980 (Box 5)
  - Meetings and Conferences (Box 5)
    - Arms Control and Reduction., 1977 (Box 5)
    - Conference on the Human Environment., 1972 (Box 5)
    - Common Heritage Conference: the Ocean as the Common Heritage (Sea Bed Conference)., 1972 (Box 5)
    - Common Heritage Conference: the Ocean as the Common Heritage (Sea Bed Conference)., 1972-1973 (Box 5)
    - Conference on Human Environment, WAWF Copy., 1971-1972 (Box 5)
    - Conference on Human Survival., 1970 (Box 5)
    - Conference on Human Survival, Articles., 1970 (Box 5)
    - Conference on Human Survival, Follow Up., 1970-1972 (Box 5)
    - Conference on Human Survival, Norman Cousins., 1970 (Box 5)
    - Conference on Human Survival, Phase II., 1972 (Box 5)
    - Conference on Microstates and the United Nations., 1974 (Box 5)
    - Group of Consultant Experts on the Economic and Social Consequences of the Arms Race., 1970-1971 (Box 5)
    - Habitat: United Nations Conference on Human Settlement., 1976 (Box 5)
    - Norman Cousins Meeting Notes., 1969-1972 (Box 5)
    - Norman Cousins Speaking Engagements., 1970-1972 (Box 5)
    - Strategy for Peace Conference., 1970 (Box 5)
    - Strategy for Peace Conference., 1972 (Box 5)
    - United Nations Peacekeeping Seminar II., 1972 (Box 5)
    - United Nations Procedures-First and Second Conference., 1970-1971 (Box 5)
    - United Nations Procedures-Third Conference., 1972 (Box 5)
    - United Nations Procedures-Forth Conference., 1973 (Box 5)
    - United Nations Procedures-Fifth Conference., 1974 (Box 5)
    - United Nations Procedures-Sixth Conference., 1975 (Box 5)
    - United Nations Procedures-Seventh Conference., 1976 (Box 5)
    - World Congress., 1977 (Box 5)
    - World Association of World Federalists Conference., 1969-1970 (Box 5)
    - World Association of World Federalists Council Meetings., 1969 (Box 5)
    - World Association of World Federalists Council Meetings., 1970 (Box 6)
    - World Association of World Federalists Council Meeting. January, 1971 (Box 6)
    - World Association of World Federalists Council Meeting. August, 1971 (Box 6)
    - World Association of World Federalists Council Meeting. January, 1972 (Box 6)
    - World Association of World Federalists Council Meeting. August, 1972 (Box 6)
    - World Association of World Federalists Council Meeting., 1973 (Box 6)
    - World Association of World Federalists Council Meetings., 1974 (Box 6)
    - World Association of World Federalists Council Meeting., 1976 (Box 6)
    - World Association of World Federalists Delhi Congress., 1975 (Box 6)
    - World Association of World Federalists Oslo Congress., 1967 (Box 6)
    - World Federalist Association., 1976 (Box 6)
    - World Federalists, USA Assembly., 1971 (Box 6)
    - World Federalists, USA Assembly Meetings., 1973 (Box 6)
    - World Federalists, USA Board of Directors Meeting., 1973 (Box 6)
    - World Federalists, USA Council Meeting., 1970 (Box 6)
    - World Federalists, USA Council Meeting., 1972 (Box 6)
    - World Federalists, USA Council Meeting., 1974 (Box 6)
    - World Federalists, USA Executive Committee., 1971 (Box 6)
    - World Federalists, USA Executive Committee., 1974 (Box 6)
  - Speaking Engagements (Box 6)
    - California., 1970 (Box 6)
    - UC San Diego., 1970 (Box 6)
    - Speaking Engagements (Miscellaneous)., 1971-1973 (Box 6)
- Other Organizations (Box 6)
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization. Includes years or approximate range of years of materials within each folder.
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Human Rights and Genocide Treaties., 1960-1974 (Box 6)
  - The Amsterdam Symposium on Food and Basic Needs., Undated (Box 6)
  - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace., 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Non-Governmental Organizations., 1971-1973 (Box 6)
  - Non-Governmental Organization Committee on Disarmament., 1970-1974 (Box 6)
  - Non-Governmental Organization Committee on Human Rights., 1971-1973 (Box 6)
  - Non-Governmental Organization Committee on Human Rights, Geneva., 1972-1974 (Box 6)
  - Non-Governmental Organizations: Environmental Issues., 1972 (Box 6)
  - Non-Governmental Organizations: Office of Public Information/ Non-Governmental Organizations Executive Committee., 1971-1974 (Box 6)
  - Non-Governmental Organizations: Slavery Conventions., 1972 (Box 6)
  - Task Force for the Nuclear Test Ban., 1972-1974 (Box 6)
  - United Nations Association of the United States of America., 1969-1974 (Box 6)
  - World Congress of Peace Forces., 1973 (Box 6)
  - World Federal Authority Committee., 1975-1976 (Box 6)